// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Android is developed by",
    answer: "Android Inc",
    options: [
      "Apple",
      "Microsoft",
      "Google",
      "Android Inc"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Android Web Browser is based on",
    answer: "Open-source Webkit",
    options: [
      "Chrome",
      "Open-source Webkit",
      "Safari",
      "Firefox"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Media Format Is Not Supported By Android",
    answer: "AVI",
    options: [
      "MP4",
      "AVI",
      "MIDI",
      "MPEG"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " In Which Directory XML Layout Files Are Stored",
    answer: "/res/layout",
    options: [
      "/assets",
      "/src",
      "/res/values",
      "/res/layout"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which Code Used By Android Is Not A Open Source.",
    answer: "WiFi Driver",
    options: [
      "Video Driver",
      "WiFi Driver",
      "Device Driver",
      "Bluetooth Driver"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which Programming Language Is Used For Android Application Development?",
    answer: "Java",
    options: [
      "NodeJs",
      "PHP",
      "JSX",
      "Java"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is Manifest.xml in android?",
    answer: "It has all the information about an application",
    options: [
      "It has information about layout in an application",
      "It has all the information about an application",
      "It has the information about activities in an application",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In which technique, we can refresh the dynamic content in android?",
    answer: "Ajax",
    options: [
      "Ajax",
      "Java",
      "Android",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is APK in android?",
    answer: "Android Package Kit",
    options: [
      "Android pack",
      "Android packages",
      "Android Package Kit",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What does API stand for?",
    answer: "Application programming interface",
    options: [
      "Application programming interface",
      "Algorithmic Protocol Interface",
      "Accellerated Programming Interface",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 11,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];